Come on, I don't wanna eat lamb stew
with my mother.
Damn. Was this close on the bra.
(Sheldon:)Now, remember, Newton realized
that Aristotle was wrong...
(Sheldon:)...and force was not necessary
to maintain motion.
(Sheldon:)So let's plug in our 9.8 meters
per second squared...
(Sheldon:)...as A and we get force--
Earth gravity.
(Sheldon:)--equals mass times
9.8 meters per second per second.
(Sheldon:)So we can see that MA equals MG
and what do we know from this?
Uh.... We know that Newton
was a really smart cookie.
Oh, is that where Fig Newtons
come from?
(Sheldon:)No, Fig Newtons are named
after a small town in Massachusetts.
-No, don't write that down.
-Sorry.
(Sheldon:)Now, if MA equals MG...
(Sheldon:)-...what does that imply?
-I don't know.
What--? But--?
How can you not know? I just told you.